FANY VEGA | LEAD 3D ARTIST



■ delavegx@gmail delavegx.netlify.app in linkedin.com/in/delavegx

PROFILE & SKILLS

Highly motivated and organized 3D Artist. With 5 years of experience, I have a strong and balanced skills both in the technical and creative areas of 3D modeling. Leading teams into creating innovative and immersive VR and AR applications.

SKILLS 3D Modeling, 3D Animation, PBR Texturing, Real Time Rendering, Retopology, Optimization, Leadership **SOFTWARE:** Maya, Unity, Substance Suite, Photoshop, After Effects, Zbrush.

EXPERIENCE

MetaVRse | Lead 3D VR Artist | May 2022 - Current

- 3D Modeling of environments and props
- Texturing and Baking
- Mesh cleaning and optimization
- Animation and Rigging
- Implementation of assets in a web engine for VR and 3D Web Apps
- Project management and task prioritization

Thermofisher Scientific | 3D Developer Specialist & Product Owner III | October 2018 - May 2022

- 3D Modeling of environments from photographic and CAD reference to be used for VR/AR game environments and web.
- 3D Animation
- Real time rendering in Unity
- UV unwrapping and PBR textures with Substance Suite
- Agile workflow for project organization and task prioritization with PI Planning

Aeria Canada | 3D Generalist | May 2018 - October-2018

- Level and game design for Android and IOS devices
- 3D Modeling of voxel style assets and environments
- 3D Animation for videogame promotional videos
- Game optimization
- Game Testing
- Motion graphic animations.

Clients: Dragon Vein, Hot potato Apps, Hino Motors, StartCups | Freelance 3D Artist | Current

- Modeling and Texturing of Low poly assets for videogames.
- 3D Animation for VR and AR videogames
- Cleaning and implementation of MOCAP animations
- Rigging of mechanical and humanoid models
- Motion graphic animations.

EDUCATION & ACHIEVEMENTS

Bachelor of digital arts and Animation $|ITESM, Guadalajara\ 2011-2016$ Master Diploma of Modeling and Body mechanics for Videogames $|Coco\ School\ Spain\ 2015-2016$

ACHIEVEMENTS

3D Modeler for KICKSTARTER Another Crusade, raising up to 15k USD and launching multiplatform soon.

AR App for PepsiCo and Mexican Football selection. Launched in the Play Store and advertise thru all Sabritas chips.

ReMix3D our exclusive virtual 3D exhibition was part of the Monaco Art Week as an virtual exhibition for the Musee Collection des Arts